orbitfiles.com 2011-06-05

# Orbitfiles - Privacy terms - Free Online storage, Free Online File Backup, Free Online File Sharing

**Effective date August 9 th, 2009**

All information provided by User is strictly confidential. Orbitfiles.com reserves the right to distribute aggregated demographic information provided by User, but Orbitfiles.com will never release the name or other personal information about User without User's permission.   
Orbitfiles.com collects personal information upon registration. During registration for a free account , Orbitfiles.com typically will ask for your name, e-mail address and phone number. Please note that the more information you volunteer (and the more accurate it is), the better we are able to customize your experience. Once registered, you are part of the Orbitfiles.com community, a customer account is created, and you can take full advantage of Orbitfiles.comservices.

Orbitfiles.com does not intentionally collect information from users under 13 years old.

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. Orbitfiles.com is using cookies for the following purposes:

\- To support security measures such as requiring re-logging into Orbitfiles.com service after a certain amount of time has elapsed.

To assist in identifying possible fraudulent activities.

If you contact Orbitfiles.com we will keep a record of that correspondence. In addition, Orbitfiles.com occasionally asks registered users to complete surveys that we use for research purposes. A link is included to this Privacy Policy wherever Orbitfiles.com collects personal information.

Orbitfiles.com LTD is not responsible for the usage of its members files, such as advertising their files, promoting their files through mass mailing or any other action. Orbitfiles.com LTD will NOT send out any mass mailing containing files to be downloaded hence cannot be held responsible. 

Users who use any Orbitfiles.com LTD email address to send out unsolicited emails will be reported to FBI.

Orbitfiles.com is using Paypal.com and Avangate.com processing platforms to charge users for its paid subscription plans and it is not keeping any credit card data on its servers. 

To opt out from Orbitfiles.com mailing list, user needs to select appropriate option at "My Account " panel.  
Changes to Privacy policy will be announced at Orbitfiles.com official blog at [http://blog.orbitfiles.com](http://blog.orbitfiles.com/) as well as by emailing all users.   
It is Orbitfiles.com policy to respect the privacy of users for the SERVICE. Therefore, Orbitfiles.com will not monitor, edit, or disclose any personal information about you or the files you upload , including their contents, without your prior permission unless Orbitfiles.com in its sole discretion believes that such action is necessary to: (1) comply with legal process; (2) otherwise protect the legal rights of Orbitfiles.com; (3) enforce the TERMS; or (4) protect the interests of users for the SERVICE or others. Orbitfiles.com may on occasion provide certain user information in anonymous, aggregate form to third parties such as advertisers for demographic purposes. However, Orbitfiles.com will not provide any 3rd party entities with your email address or other contact information. This SERVICE is not intended to be used for unsolicited email or spam. Your email address may be used in the following ways: (1) to send you a welcome email after successful registration; (2) to send you an email with any error messages concerning the files you uploaded or update for any service interruption due to technical reasons; (3) to periodically send you an email containing announcements from Orbitfiles.com

In the event of a merger, users' information and data will be part of the assets transferred. In such an event users will notified by email or by a post on our official blog at [http://blog.orbitfiles.com](http://blog.orbitfiles.com/)

Orbitfiles.com [admin@orbitfiles.com](mailto:admin@orbitfiles.com)
